Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 1707 Records WAG.298
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Agency Files, 1947-2007
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Job Descriptions (Local 253), 1988-2000; cuid7001 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Job Descriptions (Local 253), 2000-2004; cuid7002 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Job Descriptions (Local 253), 2002, undated; cuid7003 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Job Descriptions (Local 253), 2003; cuid7004 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Layoffs and Transfers (Local 253), 2004; cuid7005 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Probationary Extensions (Local 253), 2000-2001; cuid7006 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Suspension/Termination Notices (Local 253), 2000-2001; cuid7007 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Various (Local 253), 2001; cuid7008 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Shorefront YM-YWHA of Brighton-Manhattan Beach: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1995-1997; cuid7009 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Shorefront YM-YWHA of Brighton-Manhattan Beach: Grievances (Local 215), 1988-2000; cuid7010 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Shorefront YM-YWHA of Brighton-Manhattan Beach: Grievance--Debra Burns (Local 215), 1997-1999; cuid7011 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Shorefront YM-YWHA of Brighton-Manhattan Beach: Grievance--Tatiana Plaxina (Local 215), 1998-1999; cuid7012 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Shorefront YM-YWHA of Brighton-Manhattan Beach: Grievance--Alla Ronin (Local 215), 1994-1997; cuid7013 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Shorefront YM-YWHA of Brighton-Manhattan Beach: Grievance--Stella Weisberg (Local 215), 1997-1999; cuid7014 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Shorefront YM-YWHA of Brighton-Manhattan Beach: Personnel (Local 215), 1993-1999; cuid7015 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - St. Christopher's-Jennie Clarkson Child Care Services, Inc.: Bargaining (Local 215), 1997; cuid7016 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - St. Christopher's-Jennie Clarkson Child Care Services, Inc.: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files/General Administrative (Local 215), 1996-1997; cuid7017 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - St. Mary's Children and Family Services: Reports, 2002; cuid7018 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - St. Mary's Children and Family Services (also Sisters of Mercy, Angel Guardian Children and Family Services): Unfair Labor Practices, NLRB Arbitration, 2004-2005; cuid7019 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Susan E. Wagner Day Care Center: Grievances (Local 205), 1989; cuid7020 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Union Child Day Care Center, Inc.: Bargaining [Local 205], 1996; cuid7021 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Union of American Hebrew Congregations: Bargaining (Local 107), [1981]-1996; cuid7022 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Bargaining (Local 107), 1950-1955; cuid7023 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Bargaining (Local 107), 1956-1964; cuid7024 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Bargaining (Local 107), 1966-1970; cuid7025 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Bargaining (Local 107), 1972-1978; cuid7026 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Bargaining (Local 107), 1981-1983; cuid7027 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Bargaining (Local 107), 1985-2005; cuid7028 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Bargaining--Negotiations (Local 107), 1996; cuid7029 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Bargaining--Negotiations (Local 107), 1999-2000; cuid7030 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Bargaining--Arbitration (Local 107), 1963-1992; cuid7031 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 107), 1995-1996; cuid7032 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Grievances (Local 107), 1991-1999; cuid7033 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Grievances (Local 107), 1994-1999; cuid7034 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Grievances/Personnel (Local 107), 1997-2000; cuid7035 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Grievance--Victoria Brown (Local 107), 1993-1995; cuid7036 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Grievance--Ann Plutzer (Local 107), 1995-1998; cuid7037 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Personnel (Local 107), 1995-1997; cuid7038 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Personnel--Hirings, Terminations, Resignations (Local 107), 1994; cuid7039 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Personnel--Hirings, Terminations, Resignations (Local 107), 1994-1995; cuid7040 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Personnel--Hirings, Terminations, Resignations (Local 107), 1995-1996; cuid7041 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Personnel--Hirings, Terminations, Resignations (Local 107), 1996-1998; cuid7042 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Personnel--Hirings, Terminations, Resignations (Local 107), 1996-2000; cuid7043 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Personnel--Job Descriptions (Local 107), 1972; cuid7044 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Personnel--Reduction of Hours, Bargaining Unit Members (Local 107), 1995-2000; cuid7045 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Personnel--Retirement Plan (Local 107), 1962; cuid7046 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - United Jewish Appeal Communities (Council of Jewish Federations, United Jewish Appeal): DC 1707 Disenfranchisement, 1999-2000; cuid7047 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - United States Home Care: General Administrative, 1998; cuid7048 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - United States Home Care: DC 1707 NLRB Case, 1999; cuid7049 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - United Synagogue of Conservative Judaism: Bargaining (Local 253), 1995; cuid7050 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - University Settlement: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files, 1995-1997; cuid7051 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Utopia Children's Center: Grievances, 1989; cuid7052 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Victims Information Bureau of Suffolk, Inc.: Bargaining, 1995-1996; cuid7053 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - VNS Group Home Health Care: Bargaining, 2001; cuid7054 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Visiting Nurse Services (VNS): Grievance/Personnel, 2000; cuid7055 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - West Bronx Jewish Community Center: Bargaining, 1954-[1968]; cuid7056 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Women's American ORT/American ORT: Bargaining (Local 107), 1995-1998; cuid7057 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Women's American ORT/American ORT: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 107), 1994-1998; cuid7058 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Women's American ORT/American ORT: Grievances (Local 107), 1994-1999; cuid7059 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Women's American ORT/American ORT: Personnel (Local 107), 1994-1998; cuid7060 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - YM and YWHA of Boro Park: Bargaining (Local 215), 1949-1959; cuid7061 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - YM and YWHA of Boro Park: Bargaining (Local 215), 1960-1968; cuid7062 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - YM and YWHA of Boro Park: Bargaining (Local 215), 1973-1975; cuid7063 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - YM and YWHA of Boro Park: Grievance (Local 215), 1992; cuid7064 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - YM-YWHA of Mid-Westchester: Bargaining/DC 1707 Staff Reprentative Files (Local 215), 1996-1997; cuid7065 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - YM-YWHA of Mid-Westchester: General Administrative (Local 215), 1994-1995; cuid7066 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - YM-YWHA of Mid-Westchester: Grievances (Local 215), 1994-1999; cuid7067 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - YM-YWHA of Mid-Westchester: Personnel (Local 215), 1993-1999; cuid7068 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - YM and YWHA of Washington Heights and Inwood: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1995-1996; cuid7069 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - YM and YWHA of Washington Heights and Inwood: Grievances (Local 215), 1998-2000; cuid7070 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - YM and YWHA of Washington Heights and Inwood: Grievance--Veronica McKenzie (Local 215), 1993-1995; cuid7071 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - YM and YWHA of Washington Heights and Inwood: Personnel (Local 215), 1994-2000; cuid7072 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - YM and YWHA of Washington Heights and Inwood: Project Hope (Local 215), 1997; cuid7073 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - YM and YWHA Senior Housing Development Fund Corporation: Bargaining (Local 215), 1974-2006; cuid7074 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Zionist Organization of America: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 107), 1995-1996; cuid7075 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Multiple Agencies: DC 1707 Staff Representative File (Locals 95/205), 2004-2005; cuid7076 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Multiple Agencies: Bargaining, Grievances (10 reels of 16 mm microfilm), 1950-1990; cuid7077 (Box 47)
- Series IV: Officers and Staff-Administrative Files, 1962-2004
  - Subseries IV:A: Local 1707, 1962-1965.
    One file, which includes mostly correspondence between Local 1707 officers (especially Benjamin Bially, Executive Director, 1963-1968) and AFSCME (including AFSCME President Jerry Wurf) over union procedural matters and organizing.
    - Correspondence, General Administrative, 1962-1965; cuid7078 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Subseries IV:B: Raglan George, Jr., 1973-2002.
    Raglan George, Jr. was elected Executive Director of 1707 in 2002. Previous roles within the Council included director of Local 95 (Head Start) and Local 205 (Day Care Employees). Material in this subseries (approximately three boxes of records) generally relates to the administration and concerns of these locals and predates George's tenure as Executive Director.
    - Administration for Children and Families (ACF), 1992-1996; cuid7079 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Agency for Child Development (ACD)--3% Cut, 1996-1997; cuid7080 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Agenda for Children Tomorrow (ACT), 1992-1993; cuid7081 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Agenda for Children Tomorrow (ACT), 1994-1997; cuid7082 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Dues Reporting, 1997; cuid7083 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Pension, 1993-1995; cuid7084 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Child Care, 1997-1998, undated; cuid7085 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Child Care Campaigns, 1997-1998; cuid7086 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Child Care Reports, 1993-1997; cuid7087 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Citizens' Committee for Children, 2000, undated; cuid7088 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - City Project, 1995-1996; cuid7089 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Clippings/Press Releases, 1997, undated; cuid7090 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU), 1986-1997; cuid7091 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Committee on General Welfare Hearings, 1993-1997; cuid7092 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Conferences/Workshops, 1997, undated; cuid7093 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Cornell Child Care Project, 1996-1997; cuid7094 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1996-1998, undated; cuid7095 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Memoranda, Flyers, 1998, undated; cuid7096 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Cultural Institutions Retirement System (CIRS), 1995-1998; cuid7097 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Day Care Centers, 1995-1997; cuid7098 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Day Care Council of New York, 1996, undated; cuid7099 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - DC 1707, 1995-1997; cuid7100 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - DC 1707 History, Undated; cuid7101 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Driver License, 1973; cuid7102 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Employee Benefits, 1996-1999; cuid7103 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Ephemera, 2002, undated; cuid7104 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Events, 1997; cuid7105 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Families and Work Institute, 1993-1995; cuid7106 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Family Day Care, 1991-1995; cuid7107 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Financial, 1995; cuid7108 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Fur, Leather and Machine Workers Union-Furriers Joint Council (FLM-FJC)/United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW), 1987-1988; cuid7109 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Grievances/Personnel Issues, 1989-1998; cuid7110 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Grievances--Arbitration Awards, 1981-1985; cuid7111 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Head Start, 1997, undated; cuid7112 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Head Start 70.2 Guidelines, 1996; cuid7113 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Head Start Sponsoring Board Council of the City of New York, 1997-1998; cuid7114 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Head Start Sponsoring Board Council of the City of New York--Bargaining, 1982-1998; cuid7115 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Head Start Sponsoring Board Council of the City of New York--Retirement Plan, 1992-1997; cuid7116 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Health and Health Fair, 1997; cuid7117 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - High School Intern, 1995, undated; cuid7118 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Human Resources Administration, 1992-1994; cuid7119 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Interim Management Negotiating Committee of Head Start Delegate Agency Boards and Policy Committees--Bargaining, 1979-1981; cuid7120 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Labor History, 1993, undated; cuid7121 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Lawyers Alliance for New York Child Care Law Project, 1993-1994; cuid7122 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Legal, 1990-1994; cuid7123 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Local 95 Head Start Employees Welfare Fund, 1996-2000; cuid7124 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Long Island Head Start Child Development Services, 1991-1996; cuid7125 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Long Island Head Start Child Development Services, 1995-1998; cuid7126 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Long Island Head Start Child Development Services--Bargaining, 1992-1999; cuid7127 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Long Island Progressive Coalition, 1993; cuid7128 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Meetings/Rallies Permits--Local 95/205, 1995-1999; cuid7129 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Members, 1997; cuid7130 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Monthly Reports, 2000; cuid7131 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - New York City Administration for Children's Services, 1998; cuid7132 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - New York City Central Labor Council, 1991-1999; cuid7133 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - New York City Child Care Budget/Budget Hearing, 1997; cuid7134 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - New York City Temporary Task Force on Child Care Funding (I), 1995; cuid7135 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - New York City Temporary Task Force on Child Care Funding (II), 1995; cuid7136 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - New York City Temporary Task Force on Child Care Funding, 1995-1996; cuid7137 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - New York State Senate Assembly, 1997-1998; cuid7138 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Progressive Action Caucus/Committee for a Fair Licensing Procedure (National Teachers Exam), 1995-1996; cuid7139 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Same Boat Coalition, 1996-1997, undated; cuid7140 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Sexual Harassment, 1996-1997; cuid7141 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Socolar, Sandy, 1995-2000; cuid7142 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Staff Activity Reports, 1996-1997; cuid7143 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Staff Activity Reports, 1999-2001; cuid7144 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Staff Activity Reports, 2000-2001; cuid7145 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Staff Vacations, 1996; cuid7146 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Universal Prekindergarten Program, 1997-1998; cuid7147 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Welfare Reform/Welfare Reform Network Child Care Committee, 1996-1997; cuid7148 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - White House Conference on Early Childhood, 1997, undated; cuid7149 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Workfare Organizing, 1997; cuid7150 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Working Together for Kids/Worthy Wage Day, 1998; cuid7151 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Worthy Wage Campaign, 1997; cuid7152 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Subseries IV:C: Josephine LeBeau,1994-2001.
    This subseries contains a small amount of material from Josephine LeBeau, DC 1707 Executive Director from 1994 to 2002. Previous roles within the Council included Staff Representative and Director of Local 389. LeBeau was also involved with the Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW).
    - Addie Wyatt Award, 2001; cuid7153 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Clippings, 2002; cuid7154 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - General Administrative, 1997-2000; cuid7155 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Highbridge Advisory Council Unfair Labor Practice Charge, 1998; cuid7156 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Homes for the Homeless Lawsuit, 1994-1995; cuid7157 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Local 205 Awards Dinner, 2001; cuid7158 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Newmark and Company Real Estate, 1995-1996; cuid7159 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Notices, Notes, 1999, undated; cuid7160 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Professional Staff Employees Union, 1998; cuid7161 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Tyler, G.L.--Reports, Correspondence, 1997-1998; cuid7162 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Subseries IV:D: Robert McEnroe, 1982-1994.
    McEnroe served as Executive Director of DC 1707 from 1984 to 1994. Files in this subseries pertain to organizing, conferences, and administrative activities.
    - AFSCME: Council Listings, 1985, undated; cuid7163 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - AFSCME Employees Salary Savings Plan, 1985-1993; cuid7164 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Clippings, 1987-1988; cuid7165 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1990; cuid7166 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1993; cuid7167 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Day Care Providers, 1986-1989; cuid7168 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Dues Increase, 1984-1987; cuid7169 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Dues Increase--AFSCME Minimum Dues Increase, 1987-1993; cuid7170 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Family and Medical Leave Act (FMLA), 1993; cuid7171 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - General Administrative, 1985-1992; cuid7172 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - General Administrative, 1993, undated; cuid7173 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Health and Insurance Fund, 1985-1991; cuid7174 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Health Force, 1989; cuid7175 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Hudson Decision (I), 1986-1993; cuid7176 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Hudson Decision (II), 1986-1993; cuid7177 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Labor Organization Annual Reports (LM-2 Forms), 1985-1993; cuid7178 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Leadership Conference, 1987; cuid7179 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Leadership Conference, 1989; cuid7180 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Leadership Conference, 1991, 1993; cuid7181 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Lease, 1986-1992; cuid7182 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Legal: Leonard Leibowitz, 1991-1993; cuid7183 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Montalbano Initiatives Inc., 1990-1993; cuid7184 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - M.S. Thesis, Industrial Labor Relations: "A Study in the Evolution of Unionization Among Social Service and Community Organization Workers in New York City During the Period 1930 Thru 1960", Jun 1988; cuid7185 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), 1985-1991; cuid7186 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Organizing, 1991-1994; cuid7187 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Organizing: Flyers, Handouts, 1993-1994, undated; cuid7188 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Organizing: Nassau, Suffolk Counties, 1982-1987; cuid7189 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Organizing: New York State (Upstate) (I), 1993-1994; cuid7190 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Organizing: New York State (Upstate) (II), 1993-1994; cuid7191 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Organizing/Agencies: New York State (Upstate), 1993-1994; cuid7192 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Organizing/Agencies: New York State (Upstate), "AFSCME for Report", 1993-1994; cuid7193 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Organizing Grant, AFSCME, 1984-1993; cuid7194 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Per Capita Tax Payments, 1986-1993; cuid7195 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Puerto Rican Association for Community Affairs: Jurisdictional Dispute with Local 1199, 1993; cuid7196 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Safety and Health, 1986-1991; cuid7197 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Staff Conference, Dec 1992; cuid7198 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Subseries IV:E: Richard Morton, 1971-1984.
    One file of administrative material. Morton was Executive Director of Local 1707/DC 1707 from 1970 to 1984.
    - General Administrative, 1971-1984; cuid7199 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Subseries IV:F: Betty Powell, 1988-1999.
    Powell serves as Local 95 President (circa 1990s-present) and as DC 1707 Treasurer (circa 1999-present). Much of the material in this small subseries pertains to Local 95.
    - AFSCME, 1998, undated; cuid7200 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Benefits, 1996, undated; cuid7201 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1997, 1999; cuid7202 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU), 1995, undated; cuid7203 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Conferences, 1994-1996; cuid7204 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - DC 1707, 1992-1999; cuid7205 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - DC 1707 Executive Board, 1996-1999; cuid7206 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Domestic Violence, 1995-1996; cuid7207 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Financial Records, 1997-1999; cuid7208 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Flyers, Ephemera, 1997-1999, undated; cuid7209 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Head Start, 1988-1992; cuid7210 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Head Start: Personnel Issues, 1991-1996; cuid7211 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Local 95, 1991-1999; cuid7212 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Local 95 Executive Board, 1992-1997; cuid7213 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Local 95 Executive Board, 1995-1996; cuid7214 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund (I), 1993-1996; cuid7215 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund (II), 1993-1996; cuid7216 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Local 95 Negotiations, 1996-1997; cuid7217 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - New York City Central Labor Council, 1996-1997; cuid7218 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Notes, Meeting Minutes, 1992-1999, undated; cuid7219 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Reports, 1997-1998, undated; cuid7220 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Subseries IV:G: Brenda Stokely, 1982-2004.
    Stokely served as President of DC 1707 (circa 2002-2004) and as Local 215 President. Much of the material in this subseries relates to Local 215 and its agencies, especially the New York Association for New Americans (NYANA), where Stokely was a shop steward. Items also document Stokely's activity or general interests in labor, politics and political protests.
    - AFL-CIO, 1996, undated; cuid7221 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Agencies, 1999-2000; cuid7222 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Agencies, 2000, undated; cuid7223 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Agencies: Bargaining/Grievances/Personnel (Local 215), 1997-1999; cuid7224 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Agencies: Bargaining/Grievances/Personnel (Local 215), 1997-2000; cuid7225 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Agencies: Correspondence, 1994-1995; cuid7226 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Agencies: Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS), 1994-1995; cuid7227 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Agencies: Grievances/Personnel (Local 215), 1993-1996; cuid7228 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Agencies: Grievance, 1994-1996; cuid7229 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Agencies: Grievance, 1995-1999; cuid7230 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Agencies: Grievances, 1996-1998; cuid7231 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Agencies: Grievances, 1997; cuid7232 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Agencies: Grievance--Isaac Ovadiah, 1994-1995; cuid7233 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Benefits, 1999; cuid7234 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Class Action Case, 2003-2004; cuid7235 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Committees/Actions, 2003; cuid7236 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Contracts, 1996-2000; cuid7237 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--General Administrative, 1987-2003; cuid7238 (Box 39, Folder 13)